{"id":"67a4e71d4f9bb","title":"test","creator_email":"ipssi@ecole.net","creator_name":"Tyia Atwi","school_name":"","created_at":"2025-02-06 16:45:17","status":"active","questions":[]}
{"id":"67a4e7272d1b4","title":"sdf","creator_email":"ipssi@ecole.net","creator_name":"Tyia Atwi","school_name":"","created_at":"2025-02-06 16:45:27","status":"active","questions":[{"question":"test","points":"1","options":["dfgsd","fsdfsdfs","gdgsdfgsd","dfsd"],"correct_answer":0},{"question":"se","points":"1","options":["sdf","sdf","sdf","sdf"],"correct_answer":0}]}
{"id":"67a4e8ea85893","title":"TESTO","creator_email":"ipssi@ecole.net","creator_name":"Tyia Atwi","school_name":"","created_at":"2025-02-06 16:52:58","status":"active","questions":[{"question":"Qui est Paul ?","points":"1","options":["p","a","u","l"],"correct_answer":0}]}
{"id":"67a4e99a60453","title":"test","creator_email":"ipssi@ecole.net","creator_name":"Tyia Atwi","school_name":"","created_at":"2025-02-06 16:55:54","status":"active","questions":[{"question":"Qui est Paul ?","points":"1","options":["a","e","a","a"],"correct_answer":1},{"question":"az","points":"1","options":["az","az","az","az"],"correct_answer":3}]}
{"id":"67a4f2d4583c5","title":"dgdfgdfgd","creator_email":"ipssi@ecole.net","creator_name":"Tyia Atwi","school_name":"","created_at":"2025-02-06 17:35:16","status":"active","questions":[{"question":"dfgdfg","points":"1","options":["dfg","dfg","dfg","dfg"],"correct_answer":3}]}
{"id":"67a587e56e60f","title":"ert","creator_email":"ipssi@ecole.net","creator_name":"Tyia Atwi","school_name":"","created_at":"2025-02-07 04:11:17","status":"active","questions":[{"question":"erterterte","points":"1","options":["ert","ert","et","ert"],"correct_answer":2}]}
{"id":"67a58a6044dec","title":"test","creator_email":"test2@test.com","creator_name":"te st","company_name":"","created_at":"2025-02-07 04:21:52","status":"active","type":"company","questions":[{"question":"dsdfd","points":1,"type":"qcm","options":["sdfs","sdf","sf","sdf"],"correct_answer":2},{"question":"Qui est Paul ?","points":1,"type":"free","description":""}],"responses":[]}
{"id":"67a593d0d7ae1","title":"efzef","creator_email":"ipssi@ecole.net","creator_name":"Tyia Atwi","school_name":"","created_at":"2025-02-07 05:02:08","status":"active","questions":[{"question":"zefzef","points":"1","options":["zef","zef","zef","zef"],"correct_answer":3}]}
{"id":"67a59ef8b1443","title":"vrai quiz","creator_email":"ipssi@ecole.net","creator_name":"Tyia Atwi","school_name":"","created_at":"2025-02-07 05:49:44","status":"active","questions":[{"question":"2*2","points":"1","options":["2","22","4","42"],"correct_answer":2},{"question":"Ayoub ?","points":"9","options":["oui","pourquoi pas","s\u00fbrement","mmhhh ho que oui"],"correct_answer":3}]}
{"id":"67a5a175ee746","title":"test encore","creator_email":"ipssi@ecole.net","creator_name":"Tyia Atwi","school_name":"","created_at":"2025-02-07 06:00:21","status":"active","questions":[{"question":"efzefze","points":"1","options":["df","sdfs","sfds","df"],"correct_answer":0},{"question":"sdfsdf","points":"1","options":["sdf","sdf","sdf","sdf"],"correct_answer":2}]}
{"id":"67a5a2a7578dc","title":"encoreet encoer","creator_email":"ipssi@ecole.net","creator_name":"Tyia Atwi","school_name":"","created_at":"2025-02-07 06:05:27","status":"active","questions":[{"question":"Qui est Paul ?","points":"1","options":["toi","moi","lui","nous"],"correct_answer":3},{"question":"2*2","points":"1","options":["4","'4","df","qdc"],"correct_answer":0},{"question":"dfgdfg","points":"1","options":["?","erfe","efer","zrferf"],"correct_answer":0}]}
{"id":"67a5a33f78132","title":"jh","creator_email":"ipssi@ecole.net","creator_name":"Tyia Atwi","school_name":"","created_at":"2025-02-07 06:07:59","status":"active","questions":[{"question":"ze","points":"1","options":["zef","erg","erg","reg"],"correct_answer":0},{"question":"zef","points":"1","options":["zef","zef","zef","zef"],"correct_answer":1}]}
